<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LIVE IN LAB</string>
    <string name="title_activity_welcome_page">WelcomePage</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>
    <string name="get_started_by_entering_your_academic_scores">Get started by entering your Academic Scores</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about_stream1">AboutStream1</string>

    <string name="Civil">This course is a fascinating journey into the design, construction, and maintenance of the physical and natural environment.\n\n
        As a Civil Engineering student, you\'ll delve into subjects like structural analysis, transportation engineering, and environmental sustainability, gaining the knowledge and skills to shape the infrastructure that defines our communities.\n\n
        Get ready to build a foundation for a fulfilling career, where every project becomes a testament to your creativity and problem-solving abilities</string>

    <string name="CSE">Welcome to the dynamic world of Computer Science.\n\nEmbark on a thrilling journey where innovation meets technology, and creativity converges with logic.\n\n0A course designed to equip you with the skills and knowledge needed to navigate the ever-evolving landscape of computing.\n\nFrom algorithms to artificial intelligence, programming to problem-solving, discover the limitless possibilities that await you in the fascinating realm of Computer Science.\n\nJoin to explore the frontiers of technology and shape the future of digital innovation</string>

    <string name="EEE">Welcome to the electrifying realm of Electrical Engineering.\n\n
        Unleash your potential as you delve into the fascinating world where circuits come to life, and power meets precision.\n\n
        This is a gateway to understanding the intricacies of electrical systems, from designing circuits to powering sustainable solutions.\n\n
        Get ready to spark innovation, illuminate ideas, and electrify your future.\n\n
        Join on a journey where creativity and engineering converge to shape a brighter and more connected world.\n\n
        Let the sparks fly as you embark on a thrilling adventure in Electrical Engineering!</string>

    <string name="Chem">Step into the captivating world of Chemical Engineering.\n\n
        Dive into a realm where science meets innovation and discover the art of transforming molecules into impactful solutions.\n\n
        This course offers a gateway to unraveling the mysteries of matter, from designing processes to creating sustainable solutions.\n\n
        Join to explore the fascinating intersection of chemistry, engineering, and technology.\n\n
        Get ready to unleash your creativity, solve real-world challenges, and shape a cleaner, brighter future through the marvels of Chemical Engineering.\n\n
        Embrace the journey of discovery and innovation that awaits you!</string>

    <string name="Mech">Welcome to the dynamic universe of Mechanical Engineering.\n\n
        Embark on a thrilling adventure where innovation and design converge to shape the future.\n\n
        This course is a gateway to understanding the principles of mechanics, materials, and machines that power the world around us.\n\n
        From cutting-edge technology to sustainable solutions, dive into a curriculum that prepares you to engineer solutions for a diverse range of challenges.\n\n
        Join the pursuit of knowledge, creativity, and hands-on problem-solving.\n\n
        Let the gears of your imagination turn as you explore the exciting world of Mechanical Engineering.\n\n
        Your journey to transform ideas into reality begins here!</string>
</resources>